Personal Details

Name : Shlok Koirala

Address : Tamaghat, Panchkhal- 4, Province-3

Mobile no. : +977 9862884111

Email : <u>Shlokkoirala19@gmail.com</u>

DOB : 2060/09/07 Marital Status : Not Married



Education

February 2022 - Present Kathmandu University

Undergraduate degree, BTech in Al

February 2022 Coursera, Deeplearning.Al

Professional Certificate in ML, Neural Networks using TensorFlow

December 2021 Adarsha Secondary School

SLCE (School Leaving certificate Examination)

August 2019 Adarsha Secondary School

SEE

Professional Summary

Versatile content writer, proficient in researching, writing and editing diverse content for all kinds of audience with 3 years of experience. Creative programmer, able to complete projects before deadline. Proficient skills in Video editing and graphics designing.

Work History

April 2019 – August 2019 Hamro Library

Content Writer

Wrote engaging and informative articles on Nepalese

culture and festivals

April 2020 – September 2021 FHUB

Content Writer

- Utilized exceptional writing skills to produce engaging, error-free content
- Produced high-quality, impactful content to strict deadlines, consistently meeting brand standards
- Conducted market research to assess potential demand and determine optimal characteristics for mobile devices
- Wrote engaging, informative, and entertaining media scripts for different uses

Involvement

June 2019

Hami Yuwa

Volunteer

 Volunteered different training session done in each and every ward of Biratnagar Metropolitan City for Youth development

July 2021 – July 2022

Rotaract Club of Biratnagar

Professional Development Director

- Organized Knowledge-based and skill-based training for Youth employment and development
- Organized entrepreneurial trainings and seminars

July 2022 – July 2023

Rotaract Club of Biratnagar International Communication Director

- Develop international networks
- Work internationally with global organizations

Skills

- Creative Writing/ Copy Writing
- Programming
- Concept Development
- Graphics Designing/Video Editing
- Proficient in Multiple languages (Hindi, Nepali, English)
- Artificial Intelligence/ Web design
- Networking Skills
- Python and advanced problem-solving skills
- Innovative

Awards

- 1st runner up, in robowar, at CAN Info Tech Biratnagar
- Semi-finalist at robosoccer, Delta IOE 2019
- Semi-finalist at robosoccer, MiniYantra 2020
- 1st runner-up in CodeCamp organized by Interact Club of GGIC

REFERENCE

- Adarsha Secondary School, Biratnagar -7, Morang